questions = [
    {
        "question":"Which law is broken when logging onto someone elses computer without permission?",
        "correctAnswer":"Computer Misuse Act",
        "answer0":"Copyright, Designs and Patents Act",
        "answer1":"Data Protection Act",
        "answer2":"Equality Act"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is Open Source?",
        "correctAnswer":"Anyone can use it and modify it",
        "answer0":"Sold as a lisence to use it",
        "answer1":"Person who made it has copyright over it",
        "answer2":"You cannot modify or use it"
    },
    {
        "question":"What year was the Data Protection Act?",
        "correctAnswer":"1998",
        "answer0":"1990",
        "answer1":"1988",
        "answer2":"2000"
    },
    {
        "question":"What year was the Computer Misuse Act?",
        "correctAnswer":"1990",
        "answer0":"2000",
        "answer1":"1988",
        "answer2":"1998"
    },
    {
        "question":"What year was the Copyright, Designs and Patents Act?",
        "correctAnswer":"1988",
        "answer0":"1998",
        "answer1":"2000",
        "answer2":"1990"
    },
    {
        "question":"What year was the Freedom of Information Act?",
        "correctAnswer":"2000",
        "answer0":"1988",
        "answer1":"1998",
        "answer2":"1990"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is Proprietary Software?",
        "correctAnswer":"Sold as a license to use it",
        "answer0":"Free to use and modify",
        "answer1":"Anyone can help fix bugs",
        "answer2":"A company releases the software for anyone to change"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is Excel and example of?",
        "correctAnswer":"Proprietary software",
        "answer0":"Free software",
        "answer1":"Open Source software",
        "answer2":"Closed Source software"
    },
    {
        "question": "What law is broken by leaking client's information?",
        "correctAnswer": "Data Protection Act",
        "answer0": "Copyright, Designs and Patents Act",
        "answer1": "Computer Misuse Act",
        "answer2": "Freedom of Information Act",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is not an example of breaking the Copyright, Designs and Patents Act?",
        "correctAnswer": "Using copyrighted material with permission",
        "answer0": "Making copies of copyrighted material",
        "answer1": "Publishing copyrighted material",
        "answer2": "Selling copyrighted material",
    }
]
